your sales and then the store-wide one is up here you can make it a dollar amount off let's give
that let's say a hundred dollars and this will be happy birthday doug and then you can apply it to
the whole store or maybe just three products however many minimum of two hundred dollars
they have to spend usage cap um this is important you only want them to use it once you'd be code
happy birthday doug code those should always be kept private the only one that's not is the
store-wide sale and that's because on a store-wide sale just like if it's christmas sale
you could go and purchase things at that discount as many times as you wanted these other ones they
go by a usage cap so if this was not added and he could use happy birthday doug as many times
as he wanted there's it doesn't like limit you in that sense it doesn't limit it by person and
by usage it's very specific stripe is those and then we'll just set it for ending next year
create the sale there you go it'll give you a share link which is just the url with the coupon
code appended to the end of it but however you hand that off you just want to make sure that they
keep it for themselves when someone signs up for the newsletter it is set up so that it
automatically creates a custom one-time use code and sends it to that person who just signed up
so that every person gets their own code when they sign up and it can only be used once